How many types of jobs are there here, businesses
attract your teachers, they give you pension
security, but then it
is uncertain, so in such a situation, it is
very important to protect your income, for this you
can take advantage of income protection plan,
hello, I am Raghu Sharma, you are watching
Dheeraj Kumar, in today's video we will
understand what is income protection
insurance plan, so first of all we will understand what is the real income protection
insurance plan,
it safeguards your income in any way,
so suppose if
any person dies due to any accident, his
device is lost,
then a pension backup is provided to his family
under this plan,
how do editing production insurance plans
work, whichever customer uses this line,
then some amount from his monthly income
goes to the insurance company like a china, after this, if
that customer loses his life due to any accident,
then his family is
given a sum like a dum dum Hussain Surya, now how much
amount will his family get, it depends on the bar,
after that whatever
you do with your  Want to give it to the family like a family member?
Now let us
also know about some special things related to this Competitive Life,
like for how long you want to invest in this plan, you
can decide this,
five sarees, then 10 sarees. Apart from this, whether
you want the amount as monthly income
or go in lump sum,
you can decide this in the beginning while taking the loan.
Here people between 18 years to 55
years can invest and
under this plan you get to see the
tax benefit under Section 1961 of Income Tax.
[Music]